<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Hotel_Guide</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="searchable">searchable</string>
   <string name="textView1">Hotels in India</string><string name="button">Click Here For Cities</string><string name="rb1">New Delhi</string><string name="rb2">Mumbai</string><string name="rb3">Pune</string><string name="rb4">Jaipur</string><string name="rb5">Lucknow</string><string name="rb6">Haydrabad</string><string name="rb7">Agra</string><string name="rb8">Goa</string><string name="rb9">Jodhpur</string><string name="rb">Varanasi</string><string name="b1">OK</string><string name="b2">Back</string><string name="tv">Varanasi</string><string name="tv1">Cities</string><string name="r">5 Star</string><string name="r1">4 Star</string><string name="r3">3 Star</string><string name="tv2">5 Star</string><string name="tv3">New Delhi</string><string name="tv4">Mumbai</string><string name="tv5">Pune</string><string name="tv6">Jaipur</string><string name="tv7">Lucknow</string><string name="tv8">Haydrabad</string><string name="tv9">Agra</string><string name="tv10">Goa</string><string name="tv11">Jodhpur</string><string name="wyndham_grand_agra">Wyndham Grand Agra</string><string name="h1">Alpina Hotel $ Suites</string><string name="the_ashok_new_delhi">The Ashok New Delhi</string><string name="fraser_suites_new_delhi">Fraser Suites New Delhi</string><string name="details">Situated in one of the oldest living cities of the world, on the banks of the river Ganges, Nadesar Palace has hosted royalty, statesmen and celebrities since 1835. \n The name Nadesar is derived from the Goddess Nadesari, whose shrine is located in the front of the Palace. \nSet amidst verdant gardens, mango orchards, marigold and jasmine fields, Nadesar Palace is a haven of peace and tranquility. \n\n\n Hotel Leisure and Other Services include:\n \n 1. Swimming pool \n2. Jiva Spa \n 3. Laundry \n 4. 4 hole Golf Course being developed \n5. Travel services \n6. Guided tours and sightseeing \n 7. Doctor on call \n 8. Astrologer (prior appointment needed)"</string><string name="detail1">Radisson Hotel Varanasi is a five-star hotel conveniently located in the heart of the city main business district. The hotel modern architecture, warm hospitality and top-notch services are sure to please business and leisure travelers. The Radisson features spacious, comfortable rooms and suites, an on-site spa, multiple dining outlets and well-equipped meeting facilities - a wealth of services not found at all Varanasi hotels. \n\n\n Our services include:\n \n 1.24-hour travel desk \n 2. Fully equipped Business Center \n 3.Curios and gift shop \n 4.Foreign currency exchange \n 5.State-of-the-art health club \n 6.Yoga and massage at the spa</string><string name="detail2">Stay in luxury on your vacation to the City of Temples when you book into our Ramada Plaza JHV Varanasi hotel.\n See popular attractions with ease from our hotel, located just minutes from the train station, or spend your day relaxing at our beautiful resort.\n Cool off with a swim in our refreshing outdoor pool, then enjoy delicious meals in our two specialty restaurants and coffee shops on-site. \n\n\n Accommodations:\n \n1. Elevator access to all levels \n2. Elevator near disability accessible rooms \n3. Flat terrain between parking and entrance \n4. Hotel entrance is wheel accessible \n5. Parking / drop off point adjacent to entrance \n6. Service animals allowed \n7. Wheelchair-Accessible Elevators</string><string name="detail3">The Clarks Group of Hotels is one of the oldest hotel chains in India. The splendid structure of the Clarks Varanasi - the flagship property of the Clarks Group of Hotels, dates back to over half a century. Having this heritage we believe in providing only the best of services and try to constantly exceed your expectations. \n\n\n Key points:\n \n• Non-smoking rooms * \n• Concierge service \n• Baggage handler \n• Wi-fi Internet access in common parts (payable) \n• Images Downloading facilities \n• 15 Minutes free Internet access for checking e-mails at Business Centre \n• Fitness Centre \n• Patio - garden \n• Outdoor swimming pool (Not heated) \n• Rooms are aesthetically and tastefully furnished. • Unlimited Free movies in the rooms. \n• Located in a nice and clean surroundings \n• Several Dining Options \n• 24 x 7 in room dining (Room Service) \n• 24 x 7 in house laundry \n• Free pressing service between 9 a.m. to 7 p.m. \n\n\n contact us:\n The Mall, Cantt.\n Varanasi - 221 002\n Tele : +91-542-2501011-20\n Fax : +91-542-2502736\n E-Mail : clarkvns@satyam.net.in\n</string><string name="detail4">The hotel is set amidst 40 acres of lush green gardens, just 21 kms (45 mins drive) from the airport, The Gateway Hotel, Ganges is the veritable haven of peace and tranquility in this crowded and ancient temple city. The hotel is 6 kms away from the city Centre or the commercial hub of Varanasi also commonly known as The Chowk. The hotel is constructed in the holy Swastik shape (The Swastika is an ancient symbol which re-presents good fortune and blessing). \n\n \n Accommodations:\n 130 rooms including 10 suites - all room are centrally air-conditioned.\n High-speed Internet and Wi-Fi available throughout the hotel.\n Swimming pool, Active studio, Spa.\n Three meeting rooms can accommodate 20 to 150 guests auditorium style.\n Gardens for large outdoor function.\n \n CONVENIENCES:\n \n Business Centre:\n 1.High-speed Internet with Wi-Fi option 2.Audiovisual equipment available\n 3.Workstations\n 4.Facsimile, photocopier facilities\n 5.Secretarial services\n 6.Mail services\n \n Active:\n 1.Fitness Centre\n 2.Swimming pool\n \n More:\n 1.24-hour room service\n 2.Laundry service/valet\n 3.Doctor-on-call\n 4.Travel assistance\n 5.Car hire service\n 6.Currency exchange\n 7.Florist\n</string><string name="detail5">Welcome to Varanasi, a city that embodies the spiritual soul of India, and whose beginnings over 2,500 years ago are steeped in Hindu mythology. \n A city that is the cosmic center of the Universe according to Hindu belief and where the Ganges, or "Mother Ganga", India holiest river, flows. \n A city that needs to be seen and appreciated in the warmth of a stay at, hotel meraden grand that is an oasis of luxury and makes a perfect setting for a fascinating city. \n\n \n CONVENIENCES:\n\n * Cold Towel / Welcome Drink\n * Personalized check in / personalized stationary / slippers\n * Bathrobe / choice of newspapers\n * Continental breakfast / Butler service\n * Fax arrangement in rooms / internet\n * Complimentary cocktail in bar (one)\n * Complimentary tea / coffee maker in room\n * Telephone calls (3 minutes) free anywhere in India (7-7 A.M.)\n * Express checkout\n * Hair dryer, weighing scale, shaving mirror in bathroom\n * Pressing iron/stand in room\n * Evening cookies\n * Free spouse stay\n * Choice of non smoking rooms on request\n \n\n *HOTEL MERADEN GRAND\n 57 Patel Nagar, Cantt., Varanasi - 221 002\n\n *Phone:\n 0542-2509952, 0542-2509953, 0542-2509954, 0542-2509957, 0542-2509959\n\n *Mobile:\n *Mr. Ran Vijay Singh (General Manager)\n +91 9415222993\n *Reservation:\n +91 9919916777\n\n</string><string name="detail6">Rivatas By Ideal offers modern rooms and suites with free Wi-Fi at The Mall Can nott in Varanasi. Featuring 3 food and beverage options, the property has an outdoor pool and offers massage services. The air-conditioned rooms come with heating and dark wood furnishings. Each room is equipped with a flat-screen satellite TV, electronic safe and seating area. \nTea/coffee making facilities and minibar are also provided. Private bathroom includes a shower, hairdryer and slippers. \n\n General:\n *Non-smoking rooms, Facilities for disabled guests, Lift/elevator, Safety deposit box, Shops in hotel, Non-smoking throughout, Air conditioning \n \n Services:\n *24-hour front desk, Express check-in/check-out, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Business centre, Babysitting/child services,Laundry, Dry cleaning, VIP room facilities, Ironing service, Currency exchange, Souvenirs/gift shop, Shoeshine, Packed lunches, Car hire, Tour desk, Fax/photocopying, Ticket service, Concierge service, Private check-in/check-out, Trouser press, Airport shuttle (surcharge). \n\n Food and Drink:\n *Bar, Snack bar, Special diet menus (on request) \n\n Activities:\n *Newspapers, Spa and wellness centre, Massage, Turkish/steam bath \n\n Outdoors:\n *BBQ facilities, Outdoor pool \n\n Internet:\n *Free! WiFi is available in the hotel rooms and is free of charge. \n\n Address:\n RIVATAS\n The Mall Road\n Cantonment Varanasi Zip-221002\n T: +91 542 30 410 00\n F: +91 542 30 410 01\n e-mail – sales@rivatas.com and fom@rivata\n</string><string name="detail7">A part of Clarks Group of Hotels, Hotel Clarks Avadh offers a royal ambience in the erstwhile city of Nawabs. With 98 well appointed rooms, restaurants offering regional specialties and an exclusive privilege club, the hotel promises a comfortable stay. \n \n *Location: \n The city centric location of Hotel Clarks Avadh offers easy access to the Charbagh railway station and main shopping area of Hazratganj. Bara Imambara, Rumi Darwaza, Aminabad Market, British Residency and Lucknow Zoo are some of the important places of tourist interest. \n \n *Hotel Features: \n Privilege Club is an exclusive floor dedicated to sophisticated business guests. It entitles guests to select services including a separate check-in and check-out, valet service, personalized stationary, computer and fax facilities. Conference and meeting rooms are equipped with the latest audio-visual technology. In addition, there is a full service business centre with a boardroom. A rooftop restaurant, Falaknuma delights guests with traditional delicacies of Avadhi cuisine. Gulfam, a 24-hour coffee shop, serves Chinese, Continental and South Indian cuisine. Guests can unwind with a dip in the swimming pool. The health club has state-of-the-art equipments. \n \n *Rooms: \n The hotel offers comfortable accommodation with 98 rooms. Executive rooms, privilege rooms and suites are the different accommodation options. The rooms are spacious and offer scenic views of the city. Each room has a satellite television, mini-bar and attached bathroom with hot and cold water. \n \n *Rooms: 98 \n *Floors: 8\n \n *Check-In: 1200 \n *Check-Out: 1200</string><string name="detail8">On the scenic banks of Gomti River, Vivanta by Taj Gomti Nagar provides stylish rooms in downtown Lucknow. Featuring beautiful domes and graceful pillars, this grand hotel provides an outdoor pool and 25 acres of landscaped gardens. \n Well-furnished rooms are fully air-conditioned and come with ergonomic work desks. Free tea/coffee making facilities, daily newspapers and mineral water are provided. En suite bathrooms have a bathtub.\n \n\n \n *Facilities of Vivanta by Taj Gomti Nagar\n \n 1.General:\n Non-smoking rooms, Facilities for disabled guests, Lift/elevator, Safety deposit box, Air conditioning, Wooden / Parquet floor, Safety Deposit Box. \n \n 2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Airport shuttle, Business centre, Babysitting/child services, Laundry, Dry cleaning, Barber/beauty shop, Currency exchange, Souvenirs/gift shop, Car hire, Tour desk, Fax/photocopying, Concierge service. \n \n 3.Food and Drink:\n Bar, Restaurant (à la carte), Tea/Coffee Maker, Minibar \n \n 4.Internet:\n WiFi is available in all areas and charges are applicable. \n \n 5.Parking:\n Free! Free private parking is possible on site (reservation is not needed). \n \n 6.Check-in: From 14:00 hours \n 7.Check-out: Until 12:00 hours</string><string name="detail9">Only 500 metres from Sahargani Shopping Mall, Hotel India Awadh offers air-conditioned guestrooms in Lucknow. A 24-hour front desk and free parking are available. The on-site Cafe 32 serves a selection of Indian, Continental, Chinese and local cuisines. The spacious guestrooms all come with a flat-screen TV, a minibar and a sofa. The en suite bathrooms are equipped with a shower and free toiletries. Hotel India Awadh is 4 km from Fun Republic. Both Lucknow Airport and Lucknow Railway Station are 12 km away. Alambagh Bus Station is 13 km from the hotel. \n \n *Facilities of Hotel India Awadh:-\n \n \n 1.General:\n Lift/elevator, Air conditioning, Fan \n \n 2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Business centre, Babysitting/child services, Laundry, Dry cleaning, Currency exchange, Car hire, Tour desk \n \n 3.Food and Drink:\n Restaurant, Minibar \n\n 4.Media and Technology:\n Satellite Channels, Flat-screen TV , Telephone \n \n 5.Check-in:From 12:00 hours \n Check-out:Until 12:00 hours \n \n 6.Address: 4 Sapru Marg Hazratganj, \n 226001 Lucknow</string><string name="detail10">Situated in Lucknow, Dayal Paradise features a large lawn, a business centre and a restaurant. It also offers 24-hour room service and complimentary Wi-Fi access. Fitted with air conditioning and a fan, rooms feature a flat-screen TV with cable channels, a personal safe and an en suite bathroom with hot and cold water supply. Coffee/tea making facilities are included and heating facilities are available on request. \n \n \n *Facilities of Dayal Paradise:- \n 1.General:\n Lift/elevator, Safety deposit box, Soundproof rooms, Heating, Design hotel, Non-smoking throughout, Air conditioning\n \n2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Express check-in/check-out, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Business centre, Laundry, Dry cleaning,\n \n3.Food and Drink:\n Restaurant, Bar, Breakfast in the room\n \n4.Activities:\n Newspapers</string><string name="detail11">Centrally located at just 4 km away from Fun Republic Mall and the bustling streets of Bhootnath Market, The Grand JBR offers free Wi-Fi throughout the property and features meeting/banqueting space. Grand JBR operates a 24-hour front desk to assist the guests with currency exchange, laundry and luggage storage. Guests who wish to explore the area can make use of the tour desk or rent a car. The Ambedkar Park is located 4 km away while the Lucknow Railway Station is located 10 km away. The Chaudhary Charan Singh Airport is located 16 km away. \n \n \n *Facilities of The Grand JBR:-\n \n1.General:\n Lift/elevator, Air conditioning\n \n2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Laundry, Currency exchange, Tour desk, Concierge service, Wake Up Service\n \n3.Food and Drink:\n Restaurant, Bar, Minibar\n \n4.Media and Technology:\n Satellite Channels, Telephone, TV\n \n5.Living Area:\n Seating Area, Sofa, Desk</string><string name="detail12">Centrally located at just 4 km away from the ancient monuments of Chota Imambara, Bada Imambara and Bhool Bhulaiyaa, The Maple Leaf features a banquet hall, a multi-cuisine restaurant and a lounge bar. Maple Leaf is just 4 km away from Lucknow Railway Station and 7 km away from Lucknow Bus Station. The Chaudhary Charan Singh Airport is located 14 km away. The air-conditioned rooms are equipped with a seating area, minibar and satellite TV. The attached bathrooms come with shower facility. \n \n \n *Facilities of The Maple Leaf:-\n \n1.General:\n Lift/elevator, Air Conditioning\n \n2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Laundry, Ironing service, Tour desk, Wake Up Service\n \n3.Food and Drink:\n Restaurant, Minibar\n \n4.Media and Technology:\n Satellite Channels, Telephone, TV\n \n5.Living Area:\n Seating Area, Sofa, Desk</string><string name="detail13">Tulip inn Lucknow is Lucknow first "Luxury Budget Hotel", which delivers refreshingly uncomplicated quality stay with a sparkle of simplicity. We are conveniently located in the city center and cater to business and leisure travelers who demand international standards but seek authentic hospitality and local flair. \n\n Our rooms are equipped keeping the modern day traveler in mind with facilities like Wi-Fi enabled high speed internet, telephone lines with voice-mail, LCD Television, Tea/Coffee maker, Mini Fridge, Electronic in-room safe.\n \n *Room Amenities:-\n \n -Outlet Adapters \n -AM/FM Alarm Clock \n -Bath Tub \n -Bathroom Telephone \n -Cordless Phone \n -Data port \n -Voicemail \n -Temperature Control \n -Single/ Double Bed \n -Shower</string><string name="detail14">Hotel Mangalam opposite to the old RTO is easily accessible to the other parts of the city. There are elegant guestrooms maintained with hi-end amenities. The in-house restaurant serves scrumptious fare to its diners. Guests can also avail the facilities available at the business center, and the banquet and conferencing services for private and official gatherings. Massage services are also available for the rejuvenation of the guests. \n \n \n *Hotel details:\n \n1.24-hour front desk \n2.Backup generator \n3.Breakfast services \n4.Complimentary breakfast \n5.Doorman \n6.Firplace in lobby \n7.Laundry facilities \n8.Limousine service available \n9.Medical services \n10.Meeting room(s) small groups \n11.Parking(free) \n12.Restaurant \n13.Room service \n14.Safe deposit box-front desk \n15.Secretarial services \n \n \n *Room:\n \n1.Air conditioning-Room \n2.Bottled water in room(complimentary) \n3.Cable/satellite TV \n4.Complimentary newspaper \n5.Complimentary toiletries \n6.Desk \n7.Direct-dial phone \n8.H/C running water \n9.Housekeeping \n10.Rollaway beds</string><string name="detail15">Comfort Inn is 1.5 km from Fun Republic and Lohia Park. It offers an all-day dining restaurant and air-conditioned rooms with a TV. Free parking is provided. Inn Comfort is a 20-minute drive from Lucknow Railway Station and a 30-minute drive from Chaudhary Charan Singh International Airport Terminal. Cosy rooms feature wooden furnishings, hardwood flooring and warm spotlights. Each is equipped with a refrigerator and tea/coffee maker. Shower facilities and toiletries are standard. A trouser press is available upon request. \n \n \n *Facilities of Comfort Inn:-\n \n1.General:\n Non-smoking rooms, Facilities for disabled guests, Lift/elevator, Safety deposit box, Air conditioning, Designated smoking area, Fan, Safety Deposit Box\n \n2.Services:\n 24-hour front desk, Luggage storage, Room service, Meeting/banquet facilities, Business centre, Babysitting/child services, Laundry, Dry cleaning, Currency exchange, Shoeshine, Car hire, Tour desk, Fax/photocopying, Ticket service, Trouser press, Wake Up Service\n \n3.Food and Drink\n Restaurant, Bar, Restaurant (à la carte), Restaurant (buffet), Tea/Coffee Maker\n \n4.Media and Technology\n Cable Channels, Telephone, TV\n \n5.Activities\n Newspapers\n \n \n *Address: TC-75 V, Vibhuti Khand, Gomti Nagar, 226010 Lucknow</string><string name="detail16">The elegant rooms at Hotel Deep Avadh are equipped with a cable TV, an en suite bathroom and a comfortable living area. Direct dial telephone and Wi-Fi internet is also provided in each room. Hotel Deep Awadh is located close to Lucknow many tourist attractions such as the Bara Imambara, Chota Imambara, The Residency, Rumi Darwaja and Sikander Bagh. The airport is 8 km away from the hotel. The property features 3 banquet halls with modern facilities. Staff at the travel desk assists guests with travel arrangements. For convenience, taxi service is also provided. \n \n \n*Hotel facilities: \n1.Parking \n2.Internet/Wi-Fi \n3.Swimming Pool \n4.Business Facilities \n5.Travel and Transfers \n6.Restaurant/Bar \n7.Gym \n8.Spa/Massage/Wellness \n \n*Room facilities : \n1. Television \n2.Bathroom Toiletries \n3.Room Service \n4.Air Conditioning \n5.Room Heater \n6.Hot and Cold Running Water \n7.Intercom \n8.Fireplace \n9.Direct dial phone \n \n*Address: Hotel Deep Avadh,Naka Hindola,Aminabad Road, Lucknow</string><string name="detail17">Established in 1903, the Taj Mahal Palace is located in Mumbai. Located in the vibrant South Mumbai, the hotel offers easy access to numerous dining and entertainment venues. Guests of the the Taj Mahal Palace can enjoy a drink in the informal bar, sample Moroccan, French and Vegetarian cuisine in the restaurant or simply relax in the outdoor pool. It also features a lift, a concierge and a 24 hour reception. Additional features include a safe, a spa and wellness centre and a beauty salon. \n \n \n *Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Bath / Hot Tub, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Body Treatments, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Wake-up Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Computer, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Parking:\n The hotel has free parking. Valet parking is offered at the hotel.\n \n \n \n*Address:Apollo Bunder, South Mumbai, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail18">The Taj Lands End Hotel Mumbai is an ideal venue to stay for both business and leisure. It also offers a concierge, a lift and a beauty centre. The hotel multilingual staff will be glad to provide dining suggestions and help you organise your stay in Mumbai. The rooms at the Taj Lands End Hotel Mumbai have panoramic city views. Features include slippers, a coffee maker and a marble bathroom. Rooms are also equipped with internet access. \n \n \n*Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, Picnic Area/Tables\n \n2.Activities\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Sauna, Bath / Hot Tub, Garden, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Secretarial Service, Wake-up Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Computer, Photocopier, Desk, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n \n*Address: Band Stand Bandra West, Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail19">*Location:-\n Conveniently near the airport, The Leela Mumbai is in Mumbai (North Mumbai Business District), close to MIDC Industrial Estate, Santacruz Electronic Export Processing Zone, and Phoenix Market City Mall. Also nearby are Powai Lake and Shoppers Stop.\n \n \n*Hotel Features:-\n The Leela Mumbai has a full-service spa, an outdoor pool, and a health club. Wireless and wired high-speed Internet access is available in public areas (surcharges apply). This 5-star hotel features business amenities including a 24-hour business center, small meeting rooms, and limo/town car service. The hotel offers 4 restaurants along with a coffee shop/café, a poolside bar, and a bar/lounge. On select days the hotel offers a complimentary evening social. The staff can provide concierge services, tour/ticket assistance, and wedding services. Additional amenities include a children pool, a nightclub, and a spa tub. Guest parking is complimentary. The property has designated areas for smoking. \n \n *General: \n1.Beach/pool umbrellas \n2.Designated smoking areas \n3.Garden \n4.Gift shops or newsstand \n5.Number of buildings/towers \n6.Poolside bar \n7.Shopping on site \n8.Suitable for children \n9.Swimming pool - childrens \n10.Swimming pool - outdoor \n \n *Services: \n1.Porter/bellhop \n2.Safe-deposit box at front desk \n3.Sauna \n4.Secure parking \n5.Security guard \n6.Shoe shine \n7.Spa services on site \n8.Spa tub \n9.Valet parking \n10.Wedding services</string><string name="detail20">This grand and modern hotel was built in 2003 and offers all modern comforts. It features a fitness centre, a spa and wellness centre and a jacuzzi.\n The Lalit Mumbai offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a suit press, an outdoor pool and a lift. For a quick and effortless check-in and departure experience, guests can benefit from the Lalit Mumbai express check-in feature. Guests can take a stroll to the hotel very own lake. \n \n \n*Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Bath / Hot Tub, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Nightclubs, Salon, Jacuzzi, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Computer, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Ballroom, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel. Wireless internet on site. \n \n5.Address: Sahar Airport Road, Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail21">The Sahara Star Hotel, located in Western Suburbs, offers luxurious accommodation and superior facilities. The hotel offers a day spa and elegant rooms with floor-to-ceiling windows, a flat-screen TV and a mini bar.\n The Sahara Star Hotel offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a lift and a sauna. Airport transfers, babysitting / child services, a laundry service and a dry cleaning service are available on request. An indoor pool, a safe and a 24 hour business centre are also offered at the hotel. \n \n \n*Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Kids Club, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Sauna, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Nightclubs, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Steam Bath, Beauty Salon, Pool Indoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, ATM / Cash Machine, Wake-up Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel. Wireless internet on site.\n \n5.Parking\n The hotel has free parking. Valet parking is offered at the hotel. There is an airport shuttle that runs from the hotel.\n \n \n6.Address: Domestic Airport, Vile Parle (East), Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail22">The Suba International Hotel Mumbai offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a lift and a suit press. Airport transfers, a laundry service and a dry cleaning service are available upon request. Laundry facilities, luggage storage and a safe are also offered at the hotel.\n All the unique and large rooms at the Suba International Hotel Mumbai include cable / satellite channels, a hair dryer and tea and coffee making facilities. Each offers bottled water, a mini bar and a refrigerator. All the air conditioned rooms at the Suba International Hotel Mumbai are also soundproofed. \n \n \n*Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Pillow Top Mattress\n \n2.Activities:\n Tour Desk\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Conference Room(s), Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel. Wireless internet on site.\n \n5.Address: Plot 211, Chakala, Sahar Road, Opposite Cigarette Factory, Andheri (East), , Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail23">\n*Hotel Overview :- A five star property from the Sarovar group, the Grand Sarovar Premiere has its location in one of the most happening areas in suburban Mumbai. Minutes away from Mindspace (commercial centre) and Inorbit (shopping hot-spot) the hotel lies close to commercial as well as entertainment avenues here. The International and Domestic airports are within easy reach too. With everything contemporary and luxurious, the hotel is undoubtedly an upscale property that can lure leisure as well as corporate travelers to the city. \n \n \n#Rooms in Grand Sarovar Premiere :-\n \nTotal Rooms : 98 \nSuperior Rooms : 77 \nDeluxe Rooms : 20 \nExecutive Rooms : 01 \n \n#Grand Sarovar Premiere Room Facilities :-\n \n1."32" inches LCD TV with cable/satellite Channels \n2.Tea/coffee maker \n3.Fruit Basket and Cookies/ Chocolates \n4.Broadband Connectivity \n5.Bottle of Mineral Water \n6.Direct Dialing facility \n7.Bathroom amenities: Bath Gel, Shampoo, Moisturizer, Conditioner, Cotton buds, Hair Dryers Shower Cubicle Wardrobe, Bath Robes and Slippers \n \n#Grand Sarovar Premiere Hotel Facilities :-\n \n1.24-hour front desk \n2.Air-conditioned public areas \n3.Airport transportation (surcharge) \n4.Audio-visual equipment \n5.Banquet facilities \n6.Bar/lounge \n7.Barbecue grill(s) \n8.Business center \n9.Complimentary breakfast \n10.Swimming pool \n11.Luggage storage \n12.Backup generator \n \nAddress:-\n \nGrand Sarovar Premiere \nGeneral Manager - Ajoy Balkrishna \nA.K. Plaza, \nJunction of S.V. Road and Veer Savarkar Road Flyover, \nGoregaon West, \nMumbai - 400062 \nTel. : +91 22 2871 8000 \nFax : +91 22 2871 8001 \nEmail : gsp@sarovarhotels.com</string><string name="detail24">Located in the vibrant Western Suburbs, the Sea Princess Hotel is known for its luxury and exceptional service. It offers uninterrupted views of the city, stylish rooms with flat-screen TVs and personalised service.\n The Sea Princess Hotel offers many facilities including a lift, an outdoor pool and a restaurant serving fine dishes. The 24-hour reception provides services like car rentals and luggage storage, and free parking is available. A free shuttle bus is also available. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Nightclubs, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Juhu Tara Road, Juhu Beach, Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail25">Situated in Western Suburbs, the Mirage Hotel Mumbai offers luxury accommodation with modern amenities. It offers uninterrupted views of the city, stylish rooms with flat-screen TVs and personalised service.\n The Mirage Hotel Mumbai offers many facilities including a lift, a 24 hour reception and a restaurant serving International dishes. Amenities at the hotel include a 24 hour business centre, a safe and a concierge. The hotel also offers an airport shuttle service. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Computer, Photocopier, Desk, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: International Airport Approach Road Marol Andheri East, Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail26">Situated in Western Suburbs, the Mirador Hotel Mumbai offers chic accommodation with modern amenities. It offers uninterrupted views of the city, stylish rooms with flat-screen TVs and personalised service.\n The Mirador Hotel Mumbai offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a safe and a lift. The on-site spa and wellness centre offers a variety of treatments and a chance to relax. Travel arrangements can be made at the hotel tour desk. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Bathrobes, Shower, Bathtub/Shower Combination\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Souvenirs/Gift \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: 131/B New Link Road Chakala Andheri (East), Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail27">Combining a luxurious environment with first-rate amenities, the Regal Enclave Hotel Mumbai features free wireless internet access in all areas, a free airport shuttle and a spa and wellness centre. The city centre is within a short drive of the hotel.\n The Regal Enclave Hotel Mumbai has 35 rooms and offers a fitness centre. It also features a suit press, a 24 hour reception and a lift. Guests can also find a shopping mall within the hotel. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Bathrobes, Towels, Shower, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Spa and Wellness Centre\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:4th road Near Railway Station, Khar West, Western Suburbs, Mumbai, India</string><string name="detail28">Set in Pune, the Sun n Sand Pune is a short drive from Pimpri-Chinchwad and Alandi. It offers 5-star air-conditioned rooms and a stylish restaurant.\n The Sun n Sand Pune has 139 rooms and offers an outdoor pool and a fitness centre. With a free airport shuttle and free Wi-Fi, it also offers a lift. For your convenience, an express check-in/check-out facility is also provided. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Microwave, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Packed Lunches, Bedding/Pillow Choices\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Salon, Massage, , Spa and Wellness Centre\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:262 Bund Garden Road, Pune, India</string><string name="detail29">Combining a luxurious environment with first-rate amenities, the Fortune Inn Exotica offers a fitness centre, a coffee bar and free wireless internet access in all areas. It offers 4-star air-conditioned rooms and a stylish restaurant.\n The Fortune Inn Exotica features a traditional décor with luxurious accents. Business travellers will appreciate the quality and range of amenities offered. For guests convenience, room service and a 24-hour reception are available. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Microwave, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Packed Lunches, Bedding/Pillow Choices\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Massage, , Spa and Wellness Centre\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:S. No. 21, Plot No. 3/2 Rajiv Gandhi Infotech Park, Phase I Hinjewadi, Pune, India</string><string name="detail30">Situated in Pune, this 4-star property is modern and sophisticated. Guests can make use of the on-site fitness centre and outdoor pool.\n The St Laurn Suites Pune provides a range of premium services for guests, such as a concierge, a currency exchange and 24 hours room service. The 24-hour front desk provides services like car rentals and luggage storage, and free parking is available. Business amenities at the hotel include meeting rooms, a secretarial service and a business centre. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Kitchenette, Coffee / Tea Maker, Microwave, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Shower\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Garden, Billiards, Pool Indoor, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:220 Rajiv Gandhi InfoTech Park Phase I Hinjewadi, Pune, India</string><string name="detail31">The Cypress Hotel Pune offers comfortable accommodation in a contemporary setting in the outskirts of Pune. Dashabhuja Temple and Maharashtra Institute of Technology are less than a 10-minute drive away, and the property provides free parking.\n The Cypress Hotel Pune offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a business centre and a lift. In fine weather, an outdoor terrace provides an ideal spot to relax. Additional features include a fitness centre, laundry facilities and a laundry service. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, TV, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Tour Desk\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Survey Number 208/1, Lane Number 10, Near Kalpataru Residency, Opp. Solaris Gym, Kalyaninagar, Pune, India</string><string name="detail32">1.Introduction:-\n Fortune Select Dasve is one of 309 hotel style accommodation located within Pune.\n \n2.Location:\n Ranked as 1st most popular hotel style properties, it is a convenient and comfortable accommodation option. Fortune Select Dasve provides Pune accommodation combining attractive rates and quality.\n \n3.Pricing:\n If you are considering a stay at Fortune Select Dasve, you may also like to consider Le Meridien Pune, Aamby Valley City which have the same 5 star rating and located in the same area.\n \n3.Rooms:\n Fortune Select Dasve provides Pune accommodation combining attractive rates and quality. \n \n4.Address: Patharshat, Paluka Mulshi Lavasa, Pune 412 107, Pune 412107, India</string><string name="detail33">Situated in Pune, the Hyatt Regency Pune is an easy drive from Pimpri-Chinchwad and Alandi. The air-conditioned rooms feature plasma TVs and free Wi-Fi.\n Guests of the Hyatt Regency Pune can enjoy a dip in the heated pool or visit the on-site gym. Wellness facilities include a spa bath / jacuzzi and a sauna, and a relaxing massage session can be requested. Leisure options at the hotel include a spa and wellness centre, a hair salon and a beauty salon. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Disabled Parking, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Cots, Coffee Shop/Cafeteria, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Golf Course, Sauna, Bath / Hot Tub, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Excursions, Golf Course (nearby), Lake, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Pool Indoor\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Weikfield IT Park, Nagar Road, Pune, India</string><string name="detail34">Situated in Pune, this 5-star property is modern and large. Rooms are air conditioned and feature private balconies. The O Golf Resort offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a dry cleaning service, a laundry service and a safe. Facilities at the resort include a hair salon, luggage storage and laundry facilities. Guests can also make use of the resort internet connection \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Disabled Parking, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Cots, Coffee Shop/Cafeteria, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Bath / Hot Tub, Golf Course (nearby)\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Pashan, Sus Link Road, Pune, India</string><string name="detail35">1.Location: :-\n Le Meridien Pune is located close to Tribal Museum, Shaniwar Wada, and Osho International Meditation Resort. Other points of interest near this luxury hotel include Dagduseth Ganpati Temple and Raja Dinkar Kelkar Museum. Hotel \n \nFeatures: \n Le Meridien Pune features a coffee shop/cafe, a poolside bar, and a bar/lounge. Room service is available 24 hours a day. Recreational amenities include an outdoor pool, a children pool, a health club, a spa tub, and a sauna. The property full-service health spa has body treatments, massage/treatment rooms, facials, and beauty services. This 5-star property has a 24-hour business center and offers small meeting rooms, secretarial services, and technology support staff. Wireless and wired high-speed Internet access is available in public areas (surcharges apply).\n \n3.Guestrooms: \n 177 air-conditioned guestrooms at Le Meridien Pune feature minibars and CD players. Accommodations offer city views. Beds come with Select Comfort mattresses, triple sheeting, down blankets, and premium bedding. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations with deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads. They also offer bidets, makeup/shaving mirrors, and bathrobes. \n \n4.Room descriptions:\n \n*Deluxe Room:\n \n Air conditioning \n Minibar \n Safe \n Telephone \n Hair dryer \n Iron \n Internet access</string><string name="detail36">Ista Pune is situated in the heart of the city, a 10-minute drive from Pune Airport. It offers luxurious rooms with ergonomic furnishings and large bathrooms with bathtubs. The hotel has 2 restaurants, a pool and a spa.\n The 5-star hotel is located adjacent to the beautiful Aga Khan Palace. Guests who wish to explore the area, can make use of the hotel car rental facilities. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Non-smoking Rooms, Facilities for Disabled Guests, Elevator, Air Conditioning\n \n2.Activities:\n Bath / Hot Tub, Golf Course (nearby)\n \n3.Services:\n 24-Hour Front Desk, Baggage Storage, Room Service, Business Center, Laundry, Currency Exchange, Car Rental, Tour Desk, Fax/Photocopying, Ticket Service, Concierge Service\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:88, Nagar Road, Yerawada (Adj. Aga Khan Palace), 411006 Pune</string><string name="detail37">The Hotel Vimal Heritage Jaipur is located within easy walking distance of the city centre and offers modern accommodation as well as a beauty centre, a 24 hour reception and an outdoor pool. Free Wi-Fi access is available in all areas of the hotel.\n The hotel features a dry cleaning service, a laundry service and a business centre. In sunny weather, an outdoor terrace provides a nice spot to relax. Staff can help plan tours and excursions, and can assist with car rental. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, TV, Shower, Coffee Shop/Cafeteria\n \n2.Activities:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Cable / Satellite TV, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Currency Exchange, Laundry service, Luggage Storage, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: D-148, A/2 Durga Marg, Bani Park, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail38">The Hotel Arya Niwas is located within a short drive of the city centre and offers luxury accommodation as well as laundry facilities, a business centre and a 24 hour reception. Hawa Mahal, Jantar Mantar and City Palace are less than a 10-minute drive away, and the property offers free parking. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, TV, Shower, Coffee Shop/Cafeteria\n \n2.Activities:\n Tour Desk, Garden\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, 24 Hour Reception, Currency Exchange, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Luggage Storage, Souvenirs/Gift Shop, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Behind Amber Towers, Sansar Chandra Road, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail39">The Mansingh Towers has a day spa on-site, offering a range of relaxing treatments and beauty therapy. Helpful and professional staff are available 24 hours a day. A kids pool, a concierge and a lift are also available at the hotel.\n Rooms at the Mansingh Towers offer a stylish space to relax in, complete with a mini bar. Amenities featured in the rooms include complimentary toiletries, tea and coffee making facilities and cable / satellite channels. A telephone and a refrigerator are also included in every room. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Shower\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Massage / Beauty Centre, Sauna, Garden, Salon, Jacuzzi, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Sansar Chandra Road, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail40">The Hotel Arch Inn offers a range of quality facilities and services to make your stay both comfortable and relaxing. The Hotel Arch Inn offers comfortable rooms, equipped to accommodate the requirements of any traveller. \n \n*Address:c-11/12,Main Jalpura,Link road Off MI Road,Gopinath Marg, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail41">Combining a luxurious setting with first-rate facilities, the Holiday Inn Jaipur features an outdoor pool, a fitness centre and a coffee bar. City Palace, Amer Fort and Jantar Mantar are within a 10-minute drive away, and the property provides free parking.\n The Holiday Inn Jaipur offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a business centre, a lift and a safe. The hotel also offers laundry facilities, a laundry service and a currency exchange. Guests can take advantage of the available internet access to keep in touch with friends during their trip. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Shower, Bathtub/Shower Combination\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Amer Road, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail42">Combining a luxurious environment with premium amenities, the Royal Heritage Haveli features an outdoor pool, free wireless internet access in all areas and a spa and wellness centre. The city centre is within a short drive of the hotel.\n The Royal Heritage Haveli offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a dry cleaning service, a safe and a business centre. Amenities at the hotel include laundry facilities, a fitness centre and a laundry service. For added convenience, an express check-in/check-out feature is also available. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Pet Friendly, Air Conditioned, TV, Cots\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Garden, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Khatipura Jhotwara Road, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail43">Combining a luxurious environment with premium amenities, the Park Inn by Radisson Jaipur Sai Singh Highway offers a coffee bar and a fitness centre. The city centre is within a short drive of the hotel.\n The Park Inn by Radisson Jaipur Sai Singh Highway offers many facilities including a business centre, a 24 hour reception and a restaurant serving Barbecue dishes. Amenities at the hotel include laundry facilities, a laundry service and a safe. A Wi-Fi connection is also provided. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, DVD Player, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Garden, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n 24 Hour Reception, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Wake-up Service, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: A-28 C/3 Sawai Jaisingh Highway, Bani Park, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail44">The property has a 24 hour reception, a concierge and a lift. For a fast and effortless arrival and departure experience, guests can benefit from the Peppermint Hotel express check-in feature. Travel arrangements can be made at the hotel tour desk.\n All large rooms at the Peppermint Hotel are air conditioned and offer a flat-screen TV, cable / satellite channels and a kitchenette. They come with complimentary toiletries, a DVD player and tea and coffee making facilities. Standard inclusions to the bathroom are towels and a hair dryer. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Kitchenette, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, CD Player, DVD Player, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Vending Machines, Pillow Top Mattress\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Cycling, Pool Indoor, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: 6, Subhash Nagar, Near Science Park, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail45">Offering a fitness centre and an outdoor pool, the Vesta International is a boutique hotel set in the heart of Jaipur. It offers 4-star air-conditioned rooms and a stylish restaurant.\n The Vesta International features a contemporary décor with luxurious accents. An internet connection is available for those who need to remain connected. The hotel 24-hour front desk offers an express check-in feature and luggage storage. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Non-Smoking Rooms, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Shower, Cots\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Excursions, Garden, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: S-3 Linking Road Gopalbari Near Ajmer Flyover, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail46">Located on the popular Civil Lines in Jaipur, the Jai Mahal Palace Hotel is one of the most popular 5 star hotels in Jaipur . This hotel is popular not only in India but all over the world for its superb room facilities, hotel facilities and warm Indian hospitality. The Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur is the ultimate destination for both the leisure as well as business travelers. \n \n1.Room Facilities at Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur:-\n Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur also boasts of 100 well furnished and well appointed rooms. The rooms of the hotel are mostly decorated in traditional style with all kinds of modern amenities. Some of the room facilities are mini bar, tea or coffee making facility, ensuite bathrooms, IDD facility, television and some other facilities.\n \n2.Dining at Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur:-\n There are many dining outlets in this Jai Mahal Palace Hotel of Jaipur . In these dinning options one taste some mouthwatering cuisines and can also order some refreshing drinks. One of the popular dining outlets is the Cinnamon restaurant. This restaurant serves traditional Punjabi and other tasty authentic Indian cuisines. Some of the other restaurants and bars are Marigold bar , Marble Arch, Giardino , Pool Lounge and Terrace .\n \n3.Fitness and Recreation at Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur:\n Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur provides numerous options for recreation and fitness in this hotel. Some recreation and fitness facilities offered here are Camel buggy rides, Croquet, Nature walks, gymnasium, spa, swimming pool and some other facilities.\n \n4.Business and Conference at Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur:\n Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur has become the idyllic destinations amongst the corporate travelers. The hotel has a conference rooms and two boardrooms. The hotel also boasts of a well equipped business center with internet and email facilities.\n \n5.Other Amenities and Services at Jai Mahal Palace Hotel in Jaipur:\n Some of the other amenities and services offered in this hotel are 24 hours front desk, travel desk, parking, laundry, baby sitting arrangements, currency exchange and some other facilities and services.</string><string name="detail47">The hotel is located close to a number of tourist attractions such as Amber Fort, Jaigarh Fort, Nahargarh Fort, City Palace, Jantar Mantar, Hawa Mahal, Birla Mandir and Albert Museum Hall.\n The hotel is the preferred destination for the business and leisure travellers and provides international standard of services and facilities with traditional Indian hospitality. \n \n1.Hotel Facilities:\n The facilities provided at the Fortune Select Metropolitan include a swimming pool, lawns/gardens, restaurant, coffee shop, central heating, doctor on call, bar, dining hall, Wi-Fi enabled, gymnasium, sun beds (pool), handicap facility, health club, executive lounge, room service, spa, outdoor activities, yoga meditation centre, games room and travel desk. Facilities like a business centre, conference, taxi services, airport and railway station transfers, 24 hour room service, guide service, doctor on call, massage centre, Ayurveda centre, laundry facility and sightseeing are available on a chargeable basis.\n \n2.Room Amenities:\n The hotel offers accommodation in 90, well-furnished, well-designed rooms in 3 categories, i.e. Standard Rooms, Fortune Club and Suite. All rooms come complete with in-room amenities such as cable television, air-conditioning, intercom facility, direct dial telephone, data port, Wi-Fi internet access, tea/coffee maker, mineral water, iron and ironing board, sofa unit, study table, daily newspaper, electronic safe, 24 hours room service and a separate washroom with a shower area, bath tub, hot and cold running water and bathroom toiletries. A mini bar is available but on a chargeable basis.\n \n3.Dining:\n The dining options at the hotel include Zodiac, which is a 24 hour multi-cuisine coffee shop and Nostradamus, a bar with a fine selection of wines and liquors.\n \n4.Conference and Banquets:\n Conference facilities are provided at the hotel with the help of a Banquet hall that can accommodate up to 150 persons in a theatre style arrangement, Meeting Room I (20-25 persons, board room style) and Meeting Room II (8-10 persons board room style).</string><string name="detail48">The Trident Jaipur offers well-equipped accommodation in a historic setting in the outskirts of Jaipur. Guests can benefit from the on-site fitness centre and outdoor pool.\n The hotel features a kids pool and a kids club, together with a lift. Business travellers will appreciate the quality and range of amenities offered. The hotel also provides superb facilities for business meetings and events. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, In Room Movies, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Bathrobes, Towels, Shower, Kids Club, Bedding/Pillow Choices\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Ticket Service, Luggage Storage, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Amber Fort Road, Opposite Jal Mahal, Jaipur, India</string><string name="detail49">Hotel Clarks Amer, Jaipur is a premium offering from the Clarks Group of Hotels. The decor of the hotel is an ideal blend of classic and contemporary style, while its luxurious rooms and signature hospitality brings in a truly world class experience for the guests. \n \n1.Location:\n Hotel Clarks Amer is located at Jawaharlal Nehru Marg in Jaipur. Places of attraction like Ayappa Mandir (Approx. 2km) and Brihaspati Dham (Approx. 3km) lie in the vicinity of the hotel. Other places to be visited are Nahargarh Fort, Sisodia Rani Ka Bagh and Amber Fort.\n \n2.Hotel Facilities:\n Guests are ensured a convenient stay with a range of facilities like room service, internet, business centre, gym, pool, 24-hour front desk, air conditioning, conference facilities, elevators, laundry, non-smoking rooms, parking, travel desk, 24-hour security, concierge, health club, sauna, doctor on call, audio visual equipment, LCD/projector, business services and meeting facilities. The hotel presents a bouquet of dining options with Dholamaru, a roof top multi cuisine restaurant, Asthan, a cafe, Poolside Barbeque and Tablu, a roof top bar cum cafe.\n \n3.Rooms:\n The hotel offers Deluxe Room equipped with air conditioning, hair dryer, internet access, mini bar, telephone, bath tub, bathrobe, bedside lamp, ceiling fan, complimentary mineral water bottle, complimentary toiletries, direct dialling, flat-screen TV, in-room menu, in-room safe, laundry bag, luggage space, phone line, table lamp, tea/coffee maker, temp control and writing desk.\n</string><string name="detail50">Walk from room to room amongst rich textures, opulent furnishings and exquisite objects art. Step out into expansive, ornamental gardens arranged in brilliant symmetry. Retire to rooms that were once the sanctuaries of kings, princes and their guests. Rambagh Palace exudes an unmistakable sense of history. It is an architectural masterpiece that transcends time.\n \nRequest the legendary Peacock suite, which overlooks the Mughal Terrace and the garden where the Maharaja used to celebrate "Holi," the festival of color and lights. Stage an evening of high romance in a private tent, illuminated only by torchlight. Indulge in a stately dining at the gilded Suvarna Mahal, formerly the palace ballroom. Enjoy a royal, feast and lounging under a star-speckled sky. Play Polo as the kings played it, or at a more leisurely pace on elephant back. Wind up the day activities in the sophisticated charm of the legendary Polo Bar. Rambagh Palace allows guest to partake of a wealth of experiences that resound with the memories, luxuries and extravagances of a bygone era that luckily, has not entirely disappeared.\n \nRooms and Suites:\n Rambagh Palace offers 79 rooms and stunningly restored suites, which were the chambers of the former Maharaja. Use of rich fabrics and silk drapes draw from the colourful art and warm hues of the state of Rajasthan.\n \nHotel Address: \nBhawani Singh Road \nJaipur - 302 005 \nRajasthan, India \nTelephone: +91 141 2211919 | Facsimile: +91 141 2385098</string><string name="detail51">With sweeping views of the city, the Green Park - Hyderabad offers air-conditioned rooms with free wireless internet access. The 4-star hotel is just a short stroll from Hyderabad vibrant nightlife. The Green Park - Hyderabad offers many services including a lift, a suit press and a restaurant serving fine dishes. The hotel staff are available 24-hours a day and can assist with booking tours and tickets. A concierge, a business centre and a safe are also offered at the hotel. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Pillow Top Mattress\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Desk, Ticket Service, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Greenlands, Begumpet, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail52">Best Western Amrutha Castle, Hyderabad offers warm ambience and rich tradition of hospitality. Its stylish guest rooms are well equipped with all the modern facilities and amenities which make every guest feel at home during their stay.\n \n1.Location:\n Located opposite the Secretariat in Saifabad, this hotel is close to places like Hanuman temple (Approx. 0.5km) and Jama Masjid (Approx. 10km). Tourist destinations also include Charminar, Taramati Baradari and Salar Jung Museum.\n \n2.Hotel Features:\n Guests can make use of facilities like internet, business center, gym, pool, 24-hour front desk, 24-hour room service, air conditioning, conference facilities, elevators, free airport shuttle, laundry, non-smoking rooms, parking, travel desk, wheel chair access, body treatments, health club, Jacuzzi, massage services, sauna, steam bath, banquet facilities, doctor on call, business services, Audio visual equipment, LCD/Projector, meeting facilities. For dining the hotel offers Salzburg Street which is a great place to enjoy sumptuous meals with your friends and family dining on delicacies from Indian, Chinese and Continental cuisines. There is also a coffee shop which serves authentic refreshing brews and H2 - The Pub which serves amazing beverages and appetizers to choose from.\n \n3.Rooms Castle Club, Superior Room, Presidential Suite, Luxury Suite, Deluxe A/C and Royal Honeymoon Suite are the range of room options that hotel offers to all its guests. These rooms are equipped with air conditioning, colour television, hair dryer, internet access, mini bar, private bathroom, refrigerator, safe, telephone, complimentary fruit platter, direct dialing, hangers, in-room menu, laundry bag, luggage space, phone line, tea/coffee maker and Wi-Fi access on charge.\n</string><string name="detail53">This hotel features a kids pool and a swimming pool, as well as a fitness centre and a beauty centre. All the spacious and large rooms at the Aalankrita Resort include a mini bar, cable / satellite channels and an alarm clock. An internet connection is also provided. The Aalankrita Resort has an on-site restaurant, perfect for those wishing to eat in. It offers a choice of tempting options for breakfast, lunch and dinner. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Restaurant, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, TV\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Desk, Ticket Service, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Thumkunta Village, Karimnagar Main Road Shameerpet Mandal, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail54">The Mandava Suites Hyderabad offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a safe, a business centre and a lift. It also features a dry cleaning service, babysitting / child services and supervised child care/activities. Guests can browse the internet with the apartment complex standard Wi-Fi connection. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Kitchenette, Coffee / Tea Maker, Microwave, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, DVD Player, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Family Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Security Guard, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Computer, Desk, Office Supplies, Supervised child care/activities, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shoe Shine\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Plot Nos 27 and 28, Arunodaya Colony Madhapur, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail55">Combining a luxurious environment with first-class amenities, the Aditya Park Hyderabad offers a fitness centre and a coffee bar. The 4-star hotel is just a stone throw from Hyderabad vibrant nightlife.\n The Aditya Park Hyderabad offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a lift, a safe and a concierge. Business facilities include meeting rooms. Other amenities offered include a dry cleaning service, a laundry service and babysitting / child services. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Security Guard, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Computer, Desk, Office Supplies, Supervised child care/activities, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shoe Shine\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Aditya Trade Centre, Ameerpet, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail56">Combining a luxurious environment with first-rate facilities, the Katriya Hotel and Towers offers a coffee bar, an outdoor pool and a fitness centre. NTR Gardens and Hussain Sagar are within a 10-minute drive away, and the property offers free parking. The Katriya Hotel and Towers offers many facilities including a 24 hour reception, a concierge and a restaurant serving Andhra and International dishes. It also features a safe, a business centre and a dry cleaning service. The hotel multilingual staff will be happy to provide dining suggestions and assist you in organising your stay in Hyderabad. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination\n Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Desk, Executive Floor, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:8 Rajbhavan Road Somajiguda, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail57">Combining a luxurious setting with first-rate amenities, the Daspalla Hotel features free Wi-Fi, a kids pool and an outdoor pool. It offers 4-star air-conditioned rooms and a stylish restaurant. The Daspalla Hotel has 110 rooms and offers a fitness centre. It also offers a 24 hour reception, a concierge and a lift. The garden is a perfect place to sit and relax. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Non-Smoking Rooms, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Picnic Area/Tables\n Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Multilingual Staff, Safe-Deposit Box, Secretarial Service, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Road No. 37, Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail58">The Grand Solitaire is situated in the city famous tourism and shopping district. The city centre is within an easy drive of the hotel. The Grand Solitaire offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a suit press and a lift. It also offers a dry cleaning service, a safe and a business centre. Guests can enjoy a stroll around the hotel own on-site lake. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Non-Smoking Rooms, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Picnic Area/Tables\n Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:1-240, 41 and 43, Parklane, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail59">Combining a luxurious setting with first-rate facilities, the Square Hyderabad features free Wi-Fi, a coffee bar and an outdoor pool. The city centre is within an easy drive of the hotel. The Square Hyderabad offers many services including a lift, a 24 hour reception and a restaurant serving Indian and International dishes. For an easy and effortless check-in and departure experience, guests can take advantage of the Square Hyderabad express check-in/check-out facility. An outdoor terrace provides an ideal spot to relax on sunny days. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, CD Player, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, Packed Lunches, Breakfast in the Room\n Toiletries, TV, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Packed Lunches\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Babysitting / Child Services, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Photocopier, Desk, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:6-3-870, Balayogi Paryatak Bhava, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail60">Combining a luxurious setting with first-rate facilities, the Expotel Hotel features a fitness centre, a coffee bar and free wireless internet access in all areas. It offers 3.5-star air-conditioned rooms and a stylish restaurant. The Expotel Hotel offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a suit press and a business centre. Facilities at the hotel include a beauty salon, a safe and a dry cleaning service. A free shuttle bus service is also available. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Refrigerator, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, CD Player, DVD Player, Bathrobes, Shower, Packed Lunches, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Lower Tank Bund Road, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail61">Guests staying at the Novotel Hyderabad Airport have access to fitness facilities along with an outdoor pool. The hotel employees are available 24/7 and can help with booking tours and tickets. There is a gift shop, a beauty salon and a beauty centre within the hotel building. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Bathrobes, Shower, Breakfast in the Room\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Sauna, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Garden, Volleyball, Salon, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Beauty Salon, Body Treatments, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Concierge, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Shops in Hotel, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address: Rajiv Gandhi International Airport Shamshabad, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail62">Situated in Hyderabad, this 5-star property is comfortable and pleasant. A rooftop terrace provides panoramic views of the city. Guests at the Aditya Sarovar Premiere can enjoy a rejuvenating treatment or massage at the on-site day spa. Business amenities include meeting rooms and a 24 hour business centre. An outdoor pool, a 24 hour reception and a lift are also available to guests. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Air Conditioned, Non-Smoking Rooms, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, Bathrobes, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Garden, Playground, Lake, Child Pool, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Gachibowli, Hitec City, Landmark DLF Cyber City, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail63">Offering stylish rooms complete with mini bars and flat-screen TVs, this luxurious hotel offers an indoor pool and a spa and wellness centre. The city centre is within a short drive of the hotel. The Hotel Avasa offers a convenient 24-hour reception as well as a concierge, a lift and a business centre. Fitness facilities are available on site, and guests can take advantage of the hotel bicycle rental service. A Wi-Fi connection is provided throughout the hotel, ensuring you will have no trouble keeping connected during your stay. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Hair Dryer, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Bathrobes, Shower\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Pool Indoor\n \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:Plot No 15 24 25 and 26 SY Sector 1 Huda Techno Enclave M,, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail64">Situated in Hyderabad, this 5-star property is luxury and unique. There is also a beauty centre equipped with a sauna. Guests of the Park Hyderabad can enjoy a dip in the outdoor pool or visit the fitness centre. The spa facilities include a jacuzzi and a spa bath / jacuzzi. Also available at the Park Hyderabad is a 24-hour front desk, which offers luggage storage and an airport shuttle service. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Bar / Lounge, Air Conditioned, Non-Smoking Rooms, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, Complimentary Toiletries, TV, DVD Player, Fine Dining, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Bathrobes, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom, Bathtub/Shower Combination, Pillow Top Mattress, Bedding/Pillow Choices\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Sauna, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Excursions, Nightclubs, Lake, Salon, Jacuzzi, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Steam Bath, Beauty Salon, Body Treatments, Pool Outdoor \n3.Services:\n Business Center, Concierge, Elevator / Lift, 24 Hour Reception, Dry Cleaning, Banquet Facilities, Conference Room(s), Currency Exchange, Safe-Deposit Box, Meeting Rooms, Laundry service, Shops, Photocopier, Desk, Ticket Service, Exhibit Space, Executive Floor, Luggage Storage, Designated Smoking Area, Shops in Hotel, Express Check-In/Check-Out, Shoe Shine, Self Laundry\n \n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:22, RajBhavan Road, Somajiguda, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail65">Combining a luxurious environment with first-rate amenities, the ITC Kakatiya features a coffee bar and a fitness centre. It offers uninterrupted views of the lake and the city, stylish rooms with mini bars and personalised service. Amenities at the hotel include a 24 hour business centre, a safe and a concierge. Guests can also take advantage of the hotel shuttle bus and the ticket desk services. \n \n \n#Hotel Features:-\n \n1.General:\n Room Service, Restaurant, Disabled Access, Air Conditioned, Mini Bar, Cable / Satellite TV, Coffee / Tea Maker, Hair Dryer, TV, Disabled Accessible Rooms, Bathrobes, Towels, Shower, En suite, Private Bathroom\n \n2.Activities:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Nightclubs, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Pool Outdoor\n \n3.Services:\n Fitness Room/Gym, Swimming pool, Tour Desk, Massage / Beauty Centre, Spa bath / Jacuzzi, Nightclubs, Massage, Spa and Wellness Centre, Pool Outdoor\n \n4.Internet:\n High-speed Internet is available at this hotel.\n \n5.Address:63-3-1187, Begumpet, Hyderabad, India</string><string name="detail66">Location:-\n Walking distance from the beach, the hotel is located in Sinquerim, Bardez, North Goa. Additional points of interest are Fort Aguada (3 km) and Candolim beach (2.5 km).\n Airport: 41 km/ 50 min\n Vasco railway station: 39 km/ 45 min\n \nFeatures:-\n The in-house open air restaurant serves appetizing food and there is an attached bar called Casa do Pasta. Guests can also relish beverages along with snacks at the poolside bar. Swimming pool is the right place to unwind after a tiring day. Round the clock Front Desk is provided by the hotel and to revivify, the hotel offers massage service and beauty salon. To collect gifts for near and dear ones, the in-house gift shop is an ideal place and to experience something thrilling, guests can enjoy water sports as well. Additional facilities include dry cleaning, laundry, Travel Desk and doctor on call for any emergency.\n \nRooms:\n The hotel has 55 air-conditioned, contemporary designed rooms with a color television, safe, kitchenette, telephone, refrigerator and private bathroom. All rooms are spacious.</string><string name="detail67">Amargarh Resort , Jodhpur , is the perfect fusion of the classic and the contemporay , assuring service that treats you like family, Equipped with state-of-the-art amenities, facilities and services at the property are focused on enabling guests to draw the most of every moment, with a wide repertoire of sumptuous food, sparking bar, a warm ambience and a quiant old world charm ensure an experience that will make you come back again and again.\n \nRooms: 23\n Floors: 2</string><string name="detail68">1.Location:-\n Amigo Plaza is located on the 4th Ward, Colva Beach. Tourist destinations like Colva Beach (Approx. 0.5km), Our Lady of Merces Church (Approx. 1km) can be easily accessed from the hotel. Some of the other places that must be explored are Kerkar Art Gallery, the house of exquisite artworks and sculptures by local artisans, and Fort Aguada, an ancient Portuguese citadel which attracts thousands of tourists for its colonial architecture.\n \nDistance from Dabolim Airport: Approx. 21km \nDistance from Margao Railway Station: Approx. 8km \n2.Hotel Features: \n Hotel provides foreign exchange facility and arrangement for sightseeing tours. Various essential amenities that make the stay easy are front desk, 24-hour security, laundry service and doctor-on-call. Fax facilities and travel assistance are some of the other services that can be availed. Guests can truly pamper themselves with the Ayurvedic massage and swimming pool/ Jacuzzi.\n \n3.Rooms: \n Accommodation is available in the form of A/C rooms, non A/C rooms and mini suites. The rooms are tidy and sport a decent decor. Aptly furnished and fitted with utilities like safe deposit lockers, 24 hours hot and cold water, satellite color TV, ISD/STD telephone and intercom, these rooms are indeed cozy. Also, the view of the swimming pool makes the ambiance indeed refreshing.\n</string><string name="detail69">\n1.Location:\n Located in Porvorim, the resort is close to some famous sightseeing places like Calangute beach(9 km), Miramar beach(10 km), Baga beach(9 km) and Candolim beach(9.5 km).\n \nDabolim airport: 35-37 km approx./ 45 min \nThivim railway station: 16-17 km approx./ 25 min \n.Features:\n The in-house restaurant serves breakfast, lunch and dinner and bar serves drinks to the guests. Well equipped business centre is open for business meeting or conference while indoor gymnasium is the right place for a complete work out. Guests can have a revitalizing dip in the pool. The resort houses indoor games room too, where kids and adults can have a nice time with family and friends. Round the clock Front Desk and in-Room Service is provided by the resort for guest ease. Other facilities comprise laundry and parking.\n \n3.Rooms:\n 24 air-conditioned and well furnished rooms are offered by the resort featuring a color television, dressing table and an attached washroom.\n</string><string name="detail70">Barsingha Villa Hotel is set in the vast Thar Desert of Rajasthan between Bikaner and Jodhpur and comprises 18 beautifully appointed bedrooms, all with private ensuites and airconditioning, two restaurants, four lounges, two bars and a beautiful rooftop garden.\n Owned and run by Kr. Narender Singh and designed by Australian Julie Salmon, Barsingha Villa Hotel near Bikaner provides visitors with a memorable Rajasthani experience, using local decor, colours, traditions and cuisine. From the Villa our staff can arrange safari tours to include ancient adobe villages, exposing the culture and colorful living of the desert people, as well as animal watching, camel rides and desert feasts. Stay with us for 3 or 4 nights and see the amazing delights and splendour that the desert has to offer.</string><string name="detail71">The hotel is raised to the standard of travellers in Jodhpur by providing clean, hygienic and quality accommodation at a reasonable price.\n The hotel is located near K N Girls College, Near Circuit House which is a prime location for any tourist coming to Jodhpur , it is 1 km from the Jodhpur Railway Station, 0.5 km from Central Bus Stand, 03 km from the Airport and walking distance from the market.\n It is a professionally run hotel offering beautiful view of Jodhpur City, Mehrangarh Fort and Umed Bhawan palace from Roof-top. \n \nRooms: 18 \nFloors: 2 \n \narea: Near Railway Station \nAddress: 16, Old Public Park, Near K.N. College, Rai Ka Bagh, India \nmore click: http://www.cleartrip.com/hotels/info/basant-inn-316457</string><string name="detail72">Bhoomi Residency-A Boutique Hotel, Agra, with a squad of professionals welcomes you to the world of extravagance, conventional hospitality and tailored services. Hotel offers a tranquil and composed ambience with contented accommodation to their guests. What can be more astonishing and divine than Roof top Swimming pool with Taj Mahal view.\n \n \n1.Location:\n The hotel has a very prime location as it is just a walk away from the main gate of Taj Mahal. Shilp Gram (500m), Lal Quilla (3Km), Agra Fort (5km), Secundra (7Km) and Fatehpur Sikri (40Km) are other places of interest in close proximity to the hotel. \n \nKheria airport- 9km (approx.) \nAgra Fort Railway station- 5km (approx.) \nAgra Cantonment Railway station- 7km (approx.) \nIdgah Bus Stand- 6km (approx.) \n \n2.Facilities:\n There is a range of facilities offered by this hotel which comprises of Multi Cuisine Restaurant, R.O. Water Plant, Internet Facility, Ayurvedic Massage Parlor and Sona Bath, Conference Hall, Roof Top Swimming Pool with Taj View and Spacious Parking Area. The hotel has a fully air conditioned multi cuisine Restaurant to accomplish the culinary desires of the guests. They can also pamper their spirits at the spa and massage centre and sauna bath. There is an added advantage for business people who can organize prominent business meets at the conference hall of the hotel. With internet facility available, it becomes simple for the residents to stay connected to their friends and family through virtual world. A stunning swimming pool is built at the roof top allowing guests to dive in and relax under moonlit sky.\n \n3.Rooms:\n Bhoomi Residency possesses 24 rooms with four categories, 8 Superior Rooms, 4 Club Rooms With Balcony, 10 Premium Rooms and 2 Royal Club Rooms. The rooms have contemporary decor and capturing ambience with comforting furniture. To add to the magical effect, the rooms have marble flooring. Each room comes with designed bathroom equipped with separate shower cubicle, bath kit, dental and shaving kits. There is installation of LCD TV Screens with CCTV in each room. Guests are safeguarded in case of fire emergency with Audible Smoke Alarm provision. With Mini bar availability within the rooms, residents can sip chilled drinks and have a merry time.\n</string><string name="detail73">Chandelao village is situated just 40 kms from Jodhpur city on the edge of the Thar. Still the home of descendents of Rao Kumpa, who fought against Sher Shah Suri, the Afghan ruler of Delhi and died in the battle of Sumelgiri in 1544 A.D. Seeing this brave Rajput General, Emperor Sher Shah Suri said, "for a handful of Bajra, I nearly lost the kingdom of Hindustan". Chandelao Garh was built by his grandson Rao Puranmal who had annexed Sirohi for the Maharaja of Jodhpur.\n \nEntering into the majestic gateway of Chandelao Garh is like taking a journey into the past. You are taken into times past and the feudal splendour of this bygone era comes to life before your very eyes. \n Chandelao Garh gives you personalised services, a one to one relationship. Rooms are furnished with period furniture and have an old world charm, for your comfort they are provided with all modern amenities. \n The cuisine served at Chandelao Garh is a treat to be savoured. We offer the best Rajasthani cuisine. Each delicacy is traditional and handed down from generations. Truly an epicures delight. \n Chandelao Village is a typical Rajasthani village where you will find Bishnois, Raikas and other communities. You will see the local craftsmen at work, the potter, the blacksmith, the goldsmith and the weaver. \n The village has three beautifull lakes where you will find demosille cranes, sarus and other water birds. You can also visit a medieval stepwell where village women in their traditional attire come to fetch water. \n Chandelao is typical of all West Rajasthan villages. The people are friendly and highly hospitable.</string><string name="detail74">Hotel Crystal Retreat, Agra offers extraordinary services to its honored customers with admirable hospitality. Its airy rooms with exquisite furnishing are aesthetically pleasing. The hotel provides state of the art facilities to make every stay a memorable one. The nearest and famous landmark to this hotel is AGRA FORT.\n \n1.Location:-\n The hotel is located at a very favorable location with easy connectivity to major parts of the city. The historical monument Taj Mahal is just 3km (approx.) away from the hotel. Other local spots at a nearby distance are Agra fort (2Km), Jama Masjid (3km), Itmad-ud-daullah (7km), Sanjay Place Market (7km), Sikandra (15km), Dayabagh (12km), and Fatehpur Sikri (45km).\n \nKheria Airport- 8km (approx.) \nAgra cantt. railway Station- 5km (approx.) \nAgra Fort Railway Station- 6km \nIdgah bus stand- 4km (approx.)\n \n2.Facilities:\n There is a wide range of modern facilities offered by this hotel which includes Internet Access, Credit Cards accepted, Roof Top restaurant, Money exchange, Ample car parking, Car rental and Spa and Massage facility on request. The hotel has a rooftop restaurant, G.M.B that serves Indian, Chinese and Continental cuisine under moonlit sky. With availability of free internet access, guests can enjoy hassle free virtual connectivity. They can safely park their vehicles in the parking area of the hotel. In case of inadequate cash, the hotel authority accepts major credit cards. Cars are also made available on rent if required. In order to relax and unwind, visitors can ask for Spa and Massage services also.\n \n3.Rooms:\n Hotel Crystal Retreat has a total of 15 Executive rooms which are spread in an area of 12.36sq.m. The rooms are fully air conditioned, spacious and nicely decorated with attached bathroom having regular supply of hot and cold running water. The premises have access to high speed internet, LCD TV with satellite channels and Direct Dial facility. Guests can enjoy chilled drinks from the in room mini bar. They need not worry about their valuables as the items can be kept safely in the safety lockers.</string><string name="detail75">Desertscape Resort, a beautiful desert oasis, is located on the outskirts of Jodhpur City. The resort provides comfortable accommodation and an unparalleled holiday experience amid the mystic desert charm of The Thar. Let the stresses of everyday life melt away as you uncover a heritageof rich local culture reminiscent of age old splendor. Guests can recharge and reconnect with their inner selves in the peace and calm of the desert. \n \nRooms: 27 \nFloors: 3</string><string name="detail76">Dolphin Inn, Agra is a resplendent hotel well known for its quality food and services. They make sure that they provide a luxuriant and comfortable stay for their guests. This hotel suits the needs of the business as well as leisure travelers. At this inn, guests can also learn how to cook Indian delicacies, speak a little Hindi and even learn how to tie a sari.\n \n1.Location:\n Dolphin Inn is located at VIP Road, next to kalakriti in Taj Nagari, Agra. Travellers must also visit tourist attractions such as Taj Mahal, Red Fort, Agra Fort, Mehtab Bagh, Khas Mahal, Birbal Bhavan, Tomb of Itimad-ud-Daulah, Mother Teresa Missionaries of Charity, Birbal Bhavan etc.\n \n2.Hotel Features :\n Dolphin Inn provides foreign exchange, 24 hrs travel assistance, room service, front desk, daily housekeeping, 24-hour security, 24 hrs Wi-Fi facility, express laundry service, doctor and environment friendly guest supplies. It has an in-house restaurant which serves delectable food.\n \n3.Rooms:\n Rooms at the Dolphin Inn are charming with good furnishings. Basic room amenities include: hot and cold running water facility, A/C, LCD, EPABX, tea/coffee maker, mini bar, 24 Hrs. power backup and STD/ISD Facility.</string><string name="detail77">Sprawling across a lush green lawn, Grand Hotel Agra, is a family owned establishment offering premium hospitality. The hotel retains its colonial character even after restoration. It showcases a perfect blend of old world charm with modern luxury and is a first classified hotel by the Tourist Department, Government of India.\n \n1.Location:\n Positioned at Station Road, Agra Cantt, Grand Hotel lies at a convenient distance from the airport and both Agra Fort and Agra Cantonment Railway stations. Major tourist destinations like Girishwar Mahadev Mandir (Approx. 2km) and Taj Mahal (Approx. 6km) can be easily accessed from the hotel. Agra is a historic city and has been home to many civilizations, Mughal dynasty being the most prominent. Many monuments were erected by Mughal rulers making Agra a treasure for historians. Fatehpur Sikri, Buland Darwaza, Tomb of Itimad-ud-Daulah, Khas Mahal, Mehtab Bagh, Panch Mahal, Birbal Bhavan, Jama Masjid, Anguri Bagh, Moti Masjid, Lower Haramsara are some interesting destinations that can be visited from the hotel.\n \nDistance from Kheria airport: Approx. 4km \nDistance from Agra Fort Railway station: Approx. 4km \nDistance from Agra Cantonment Railway station: Approx. 1km \n2.Hotel Facilities:\n The hotel is a perfect venue for social gatherings and corporate events with its well equipped banquet halls and conference rooms. It also arranges for Yoga, magic and musical show and sightseeing facilities on request. The hotel provides foreign currency exchange, secretarial service, and other essential services such as parking, concierge, Wi-Fi on charge, transportation, wake-up service, daily housekeeping, 24 hr front desk, 24 hr security, laundry, travel desk and doctor on call. The hotel has a multi cuisine restaurant Chahat, serving delicious Indian, Continental and Oriental dishes.\n \n3.Rooms: The deluxe and executive rooms are tastefully designed and provide perfect relaxation after a tiring day. Epitomising the blend of elegance and comfort, these rooms ensure complete privacy and serenity to the guests. These rooms feature amenities like air conditioning, colour television, internet access, mini bar, safe, tea/coffee maker, Wi-Fi access on charge, writing desk, attached bathroom, telephone with direct dialling and in-room menu for the convenience of the guests.\n \nRooms: 71 \nFloors: 1 \nHotel policies \nCheck-In: 1400 \nCheck-Out: 1200 \n \nArea: Agra Cantonment \nAddress: 137, Station Road, Agra Cantt., India</string><string name="detail78">Hotel 9 Star is a conveniently positioned, semi luxurious hotel. The hotel reflects the Indian warmth and novelty and is centrally air conditioned. It offers an array of impressive facilities with good standards of sanitation according to the expectations of business and leisure tourists.\n \n1.Location:\n Hotel 9 Star is situated close to the Taj Mahal which is at a distance of 1km from here. The places of interest near the hotel are Phool Syed Shrine at a distance of 500m, Masjid Barah Khamba at an approximate distance of 1km, Agra Fort 200m away, Red Fort at a distance of 2kms, Fatehpur Sikri at a distance of 45kms, Sikandra 14kms away, Douwn Town at an approximate distance of 1km, Dayal Bagh at a distance of 11kms, Mathura 52kms away and Itmad ??? Ud ??? Daulah at a distance of 6kms from the hotel.\n \nKheria Airport- 8kms (Approx.) \nAgra Fort Railway Station- 4kms (Approx.) \nAgra Cantonment Railway Station- 6kms (Approx.) \nAgra Local Bus Stand- 1km (Approx.) \n2.Features:\n Hotel 9 Star offers many polished facilities to its guests like hygiene and perfect maintenance, abundance of open spaces, lawns and gardens and the restaurant. The in house multi cuisine restaurant, 9 Star offers a diversity of appetizing cuisines to satisfy the palates of the guests. The food of the restaurant is like homemade luscious food pleasing the taste buds of all. Other facilities offered by the hotel are room service, acceptance of all major credit cards, 24 hour currency exchange, fax and internet facilities, travel desk, same day laundry facilities and parking facilities.\n \n3.Rooms:\n Hotel 9 Star offers 19 rooms with two classy categories, Deluxe Rooms and Standard rooms. The well maintained rooms with sophisticated surroundings are air conditioned and well appointed with direct dial telephones for local STD/ISD calls, LED TV with 24 hour satellite transmission, full length mirror and safe deposit lockers. Each room has en suite bathroom with essential toiletries and instant hot water. The walls of the stylish Deluxe Rooms have soft colours while the impressive Standard Rooms have decent wallpapers on the walls.\n</string><string name="detail79">Wyndham Grand, Agra is a 5 star hotel built on a beautiful property with stunning views of the manicured lawns, lovely fountains and ancient interiors coupled with modern facilities. Wyndham Grand Agra is perfect a getaway with its one of a kind environment. \n \n1.Location: \n Wyndham Grand is located at Fatehabad Road, Agra. Places of interest near to the hotel are Taj Mahal (Approx. 3km) and Agra fort (Approx. 6km). Jama Masjid, Buland Darwaza and Mehtab Bagh are other general tourist spots.\n \nDistances from Kheria airport : Approx. 10km \nDistances from Agra Fort Railway station : Approx. 7km \nDistances from Agra Cantonment Railway station : Approx. 8km\n \n2.Hotel Features: \n Wyndham Grand provides conference and banquet halls for various events. Room service, front desk, daily housekeeping, 24-hour security, concierge and travel desk, wireless internet are some facilities offered. For some relaxation, guests can use the swimming pool, Jacuzzi, spa, gymnasium or dance in the discotheque. Wyndham Grand has many in-house restaurants: Orient cafe is a modern cafe that offers quick lunch or dinner. Mharo Gaon - An ethnic village theme restaurant, it serves the local and Rajasthani cuisine with live Rajasthani folk dance performances and puppet shows.Jharokha is an aquamarine lounge bar and it overlooks the spectacular Mughal garden and lastly, Zaiqa their multi cuisine a la carte restaurant.\n \n3.Rooms: \n Wyndham Grand has very plush rooms. Everything about them speaks of royalty and luxury. Basic amenities include tea/coffee maker, refrigerator, LCD TV, DVD Player, telephone, international direct dialing , internet access, hair dryer, safe, self-controlled heating system, bathtub, iron and ironing board, sofa bed, bed side electronic control panels, mini bar, power converters for international guests, work desk with lamp and voicemail.</string><string name="detail80">Spread over six acres of lush, landscaped gardens, this palace of the 21st century offers luxurious refinement. With its Marwar style architecture and Moghul-inspired domes, enameled murals, slender columns, and grand interiors, this is design that lives up to the fantasy. Located close to the city markets, nearby guests can find much to see and experience.</string><string name="detail81">The Palace was built, between 1928 and 1943, for H.H. Maharaja Umaid Singh ji, Grand Father of our present Maharaja, who had benevolently commissioned a new palace in 1923 to replace Mehrangarh Fort as the symbol of a new Jodhpur and to give employment to the people of Marwar during the periods great droughts and famines.Perched high above the desert capital of Jodhpur, Umaid Bhawan Palace is the last of the great palaces of India and one of the largest private residences in the world - set amidst 26 acres of lush gardens.Named after Maharaja Umaid Singh, grandfather of the present Maharaja of Jodhpur, this golden - yellow sandstone monument was conceived on the grandest possible scale, in the fashionable Art Deco Style of that time. After 15 years in construction, the 347 - room palace was finally completed in 1943 - and has served as the principal residence of the Jodhpur royal family since.Designed by renowned Edwardian architect Henry Lanchester, the palace is a blend of eastern and western architectural influences. Its majestic 105 - foot high cupola is influenced by the Renaissance, while the towers draw inspiration from Rajput tradition. The lavish interiors with gilt furniture and elegant artwork follow the Art Deco style, complemented by the exotic murals of the self-exiled Polish artist Stefan Norblin.</string><string name="detail82">Samsara Resort, located on the Jaisalmer road 115 km from Jodhpur in the village of Dechu, is a result of a vision, Spellbinding hospitality, Luxury and Comfort to Pamper the Soul. Set amidst sprawling desert in the land of 25 acres, this architectural marvel mingled with local craft with contextual character and aesthetic sensibility thus bringing out visual and luxurious strengths in traditional and innovative manner. The clusters of rooms with landscaped and hard caped central courtyards offer interactive spaces without compromising privacies. The low rise buildings embellished by chajjas, innovative columns and crafted openings complimented by the sand dunes view and the private gardens cater to aspirations of the modern travellers. Complimenting the architecture and facade are the interiors blending seamlessly with aesthetic sensibilities. Amalgamated motifs and colours in floor engage the meandering guests in all areas. Comfort in its use, engaging in nature and innovative in crafts is the interiors as described best. Private Gardens along each room adds to the luxury and expanse of the rooms. Water bodies and effusive green areas add to the vision of making it a true Oasis in the desert. 32 luxurious villas and 2 Grand suites with ample public area, swimming pools, recreation areas and gardens set along its private sand dunes makes it a true resort experience. Hospitality and comfort interwoven with high standards of personalised service transforms one into the era bygone, Majestic and Soul warming.</string>
</resources>